Guide to the Medical Center records, 1825-2005 RG0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Personnel files, circa 1970-circa 1989; RG0007 Series 1; 34.5 Linear feet
  - Dill, Leslie, undated (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Dobbins, Williams, undated (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Dodek, Samuel, undated (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - Domm, Bill, undated (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - Donald, Howard, undated (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - Donlon, Charlotte, undated (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Donnally, Reamur, undated (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - Donnelly, Orville, undated (Box 17, Folder 146)
  - Donowitz, Mark, undated (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - Dorman, Hamilton, undated (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Dorman, Parker, undated (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - Douglas, Harry, undated (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - Dove, Samuel, undated (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - Dowling, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Downey, Harold, undated (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Dubroff, Seymour, undated (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - Duchez, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - Dufault, Leo, undated (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - Duff, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Dugan, Joseph, undated (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - Duggins, Virginia, undated (Box 17, Folder 159)
  - Dunkley, Richard, undated (Box 17, Folder 160)
  - Dunn, W. LeRoy, undated (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - DuPrey, R.E., undated (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Durell, Jack, undated (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Dusbabek, James, undated (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - Abend, Jeffrey A., undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Department:Ortho.Sur
  - Abraham, Kristof, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Ackerman, Robert M., undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Department:Ortho. Part-time
  - Adair, Robin H., undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Afshar, Dara S., undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Department:OB.
  - Ahronovich, Margot, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Department:PED
  - Ain, Brent R., undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Department:Ortho Sur.
  - Alcuri, Steven J., undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Alele, Christian O., undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Ali, Ahmed M., undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Department:Sur
  - Ali, Nayab, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Department:Med-Card
  - Altman, Roy P., undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Altstatt, Alice H., undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Department:Anes
  - Ames, Bruce L., undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Anroerman, Richard G., undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Anderson, Andrew S., undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Department: Anes
  - Anderson, Arthur J., undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Anderson, Kathryn D., undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Department:Child H. and dev
  - Anderson, James E., undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Anderson, Mavis F., undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Anixter, William L., undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    Department: Psych
  - Appel, Leonard P., undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Appleton, James R., undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    Department:Plastic-Sur
  - Applewhaite, Osbert M., undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Arabian, Aram A., undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Armaly, Raya Opthal., undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Armer, Andrew J., undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Arons, Bernard S., undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Aurecchia, Steven A., undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Atiemo, Emmanuel A., undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Auth, Thomas L., undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Babin, Silas M., undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Ballinger, William G., undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Balla, Lajos B., undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Bailey, George W., undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Bailey, George W., undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    Department: Ped
  - Barbash, Andrew J., undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Barnes, Francis F., undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Barr, Joseph F., undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Bayne, Carole D., undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
    Department: Med/Gast
  - Barter, Robert H., undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Barry, Aron, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
    Department: Urol
  - Barrows, Diana, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Barsky, Sanford H., undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
    Department:Path
  - Barth, Werner F., undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Bartlett, Edward L., undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Battiata, Salvatore V., undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Beaver, Harry, undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Beeman, Edward A., undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Becker, Scott L., undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Belizan, Luicia R., undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Belman, A. Berry, undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Bender, Carol L., undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Benjamin, Stanley B., undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Bensimon, Hector, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Bentolila, Luis F., undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Berger, Myron P., undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Berk, Sanders H., undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Belin, Michael W., undated (Box 18, Folder 59)
    Department:Ophtha
  - Bernstein, Howard, undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
    Department:No Ophtha
  - Bever, Christopher T., undated (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Bhasin, Kamlesh, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Department: Med-Rehab
  - Birk, Peter S., undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Bitteti, Janice M., undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Bis, Kathleen, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Bishop, Norman R., undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Black, Barbara O., undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Blackbourne, Brian D., undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Bloom, Sherman, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Department: Path
  - Bohon, Constance J., undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Boltansky, Howard, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Department: Int. Med
  - Booker, Clifford R., undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Department: Ped. NB
  - Booker, Sylvester C., undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Boom, William H., undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Bottiglione, John A., undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Department:Child H and Dev
  - Boyajian, Michael J., undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Department:Plas-Sur
  - Bravo M. Eduardo, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Brallier, David R., undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Department: Rad/child hea.
  - Brandes, Julia, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Department:Neph
  - Bray, Gordon L., undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Brecher, Gary, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Bristol, Raymond C., undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Brody, David M., undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Department:Ottho.
  - Brody, Joyce E., undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Brower, Anne C., undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Department: Rad
  - Brown III, Brooks G., undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    Department:Ophth.
  - Brown, Martin H., undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Department: Emer Med
  - Brown, William, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Brudno, Douglas S., undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    Department: Neoat
  - Brunschwyler, Philip C., undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Bryan, Ralph T., undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Emer-Department: Med
  - Bryce, Peter A., undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Ceithaml, Eric L., undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Buchanan, George C., undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
    Department: Med Un-pt
  - Buchanan, Robert W., undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Bulger, James C., undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Bull-Henry, Kathy P., undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    Department:Int-Department: Med
  - Burchuck, Robert M., undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Burka, Stephen, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
    Department: Med/renal
  - Burnhill, Michael S., undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Burns, Risa B., undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
    Department: Emer Med.
  - Burtoff, Samuel, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Byrd, Edward B., undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
    Department: Neuro Surg
  - Callaway, C Wayne, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
    Department:Meta/Endo
  - Callender, Clive O., undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
    Department: Surg
  - Cameron, Ronald R., undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Campbell, Peter L., undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Cantor, David J., undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
    Department: Oral Surg
  - Capone, Helen D., undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Carlson, Steven E., undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
    Department: Int Med
  - Carpousis, Dean P., undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
    Department: Med/Card
  - Carroll, Charles P., undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Cartwright, Edward C., undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Casanova-Curcio, Velma E., undated (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Cattell, Hereward S., undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
    Department:Ortho-Sug
  - Ceithaml, Eric L., undated (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Chamberlain, John L., undated (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Chanel, Philippe E., undated (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Chang, Charles S., undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
    NeDepartment: Urol
  - Chap, Eugene J., undated (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Chatel, John C., undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Chaudhary, Mohammad, undated (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Chen, Chiayu, undated (Box 19, Folder 62)
    Department: Card Med
  - Chen, Harry L., undated (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Chiu, Wu S., undated (Box 19, Folder 64)
    Department: Rehab Med
  - Chrousos, George P., undated (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Clancy, Margaret M., undated (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Clapp, Deborah G., undated (Box 19, Folder 67)
    Department:Health care sci/Child Health and dev.
  - Claunch, Alan B., undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Leslie G., undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Department:Health care sci/Med
  - Cohen, Steven E., undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Department:Phys/Asst
  - Coldwell, Douglas M., undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Coleman, Norman K., undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Coleman Jr. Stanford J., undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Department: Child health and dev.
  - Conant, Richard, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Conlon, Joseph F., undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Connally, Nathaniel T., undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Department: Med un/pt
  - Connelly, Neville K., undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Constantinople, Nicholas L., undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Conway, Steven J., undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Int.Department: Med
  - Cooper, James K., undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Department: Med.Un-fl
  - Decker, Catherine F., undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Copeland, Jay S., undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Cove, Laurence A., undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Department:Asst.Clinical prof/child h and dev.
  - Cowen, Norman J., undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Cowell, Pamela D., undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Crantz, Joanne G., undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Cowtun, Marguerite L., undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Craft, John B., undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Cullen, William, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Cushner, Gilbert B., undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Cutler, Neal R., undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Cutting, Mary E., undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - D'Agostino, Angelo, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Daty, Virginia C., undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Delacy, Lee MEmer., undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Davis, Christopher J., undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Davis, Mary M., undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Delaney, Alien G., undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Demuth, Susan A., undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
    Department: Child Health and dev.
  - Desandies, Kenneth A., undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Dispenza, Sebastian J., undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Diegel, Joar, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Doner, Kathy S., undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
    Int.Department: Med/Health Care
  - Douglas, Beverly G., undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Dow, Robert L., undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Doyle, Brian B., undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Drass Mary J., undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Dudas-Gyorki, George, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Dufresne, Craig P., undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
    Department: Plastic Surg
  - Dullum, Mercedes K., undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Dunbar, Burdetts, undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Dunmore, Gwendolyn, undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Duvall, Charles, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Dwyer, Thomas P., undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Ecker, Sidney W., undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Edelstein, Sol, undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
    Department:Health care sci/Anesth
  - Ein, Thomas E., undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Eden, David, undated (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Edmonds, Craig, undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Egan, James H., undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
    Department: Psych/Department: Child Health
  - Egan, James W., undated (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Einstein, Norman Z., undated (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Eisenbrey, Edward, undated (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Eisenstein, Clara, undated (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Eisner, Gilbert M., undated (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Ellsworth, George A., undated (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Emery, Janice J., undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Enders, MarchRehab., undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Engelstein, Joel M., undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - English III. Joseph M., undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ennis, Francis A., undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Eron, Lawrence J., undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Department: Int. Med/Indwx.S
  - Ettenson, Stephen C., undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Evers, Joseph C., undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Everson, Marshall H., undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ezekwueche, Christian M., undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fabro, Sergio E., undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Falk, Richard J., undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Fallen, Judith C., undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Farfel, Arthur B., undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Fang, Mary H., undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Farrior, Hugh L., undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fauci, Anthon S., undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Fee, Norman F., undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Feitel, Morris, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Feigin, David S., undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Feinstein, Carl B., undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Feldman, Burt I., undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Feldman, Melvin L., undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    Department: Ped/N.B.
  - Felipescu, Nocolae, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Fender, Gary, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Fenichel, Gerald M., undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Fenton, Enoch R., undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Fernbach, Nirmala K., undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Feroli, Edward J., undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Ferreras, Richard A., undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    Department:Health care sci and Med
  - Ferrell, Paul B., undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
    Department: Med.Rhumat
  - Foialco, Marc L., undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Fields, Richard L., undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Filner, Bernard E., undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
    Department: Anesth
  - Finder, Charles A., undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Fine, Ben S., undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Fisher, Jack, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
    Department: Surg/Plastic
  - Fisher, BDepartment: Radford G., undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Fitz, Marshall D., undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Fleischer, David E., undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Fleming Edward S., undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Flynn, John H., undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Follansbee, John N., undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Ford, Vivian E., undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
    Department:Nurse-midwife (Ob-Gyn)
  - Forrester, Donald, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
    Department: Oral Surg/Department: Child Health
  - Fossieck Jr., Byron E., undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Foulke, John D., undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Foulke, Charles W., undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Fox, John L., undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
    NeuroDepartment: Surg
  - France, Nancy K., undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Francis, Jack D., undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
    Department: Urolo
  - Frank, Colin H., undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Frank, Eugene, undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Frank, Jane, undated (Box 21, Folder 54)
    Department: Rad.Child Health
  - Frank, Justin A., undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Frazier, Aquinanta, undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
    Department: Urol.Department: Surg
  - Fredd, Stephen B., undated (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Freedman, Matthew T., undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Freifield, Martin I., undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Freidman, Arnold, undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Frenkel, David S., undated (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Friedman, Gruce C., undated (Box 21, Folder 62)
    Department: Med/Emer.Med.
  - Fromme, David, undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
    Department:Dentistry
  - Fu, Whei-Rung, undated (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Fusner, Jane E., undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Gaerner, Richard L., undated (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Gaffney, Brian J., undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
    Department:Asst.prof/Med
  - Gahresy, Edwacd E., undated (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Gabos, Beltram., undated (Box 21, Folder 69)
    Department:Rocardp M/A
  - Galdi, Albert P., undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
    Department: Ne Urol
  - Galliner, Wilfred E., undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Gallinek, Wilfred E., undated (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Galli, Sharon N., undated (Box 21, Folder 73)
    Department: B. Med
  - Gallagher, Walter J., undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Galipeau, Philip J., undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Gambrill III, Raymond, undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Garcia, Victor N., undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
    Department:B. Services
  - Gardner, Sheryl P., undated (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Gargurevich, Antonio J., undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Garson, Ronald J., undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Garrett, Margaret L., undated (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Gavaris Paul T., undated (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Gaspar, Maurice, undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Genner III, Byron A., undated (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Gershen, Barton J., undated (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Gianella, Ralph A., undated (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Gibbons, Raymond J., undated (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Ginsberg, Stephen P., undated (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Classman, Leonard M., undated (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Glatt, Milton, undated (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Gluck, Rita S., undated (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Goel, Naresh C., undated (Box 21, Folder 92)
    Department: Surg/Ent
  - Gold, Robert L., undated (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Goldberg, Samuel, undated (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Goldberger, Stephen G., undated (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Goldblatt, Seymoiur Z., undated (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - GoIdes, Jeffry A., undated (Box 21, Folder 97)
    Department:Dermat.
  - Goldman, Jerome N., undated (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Goldstein, Howard D, undated (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - Goldstein, Robert A., undated (Box 21, Folder 100)
    Department: Asst.Prof/Med
  - Golfo, Elsielyn B., undated (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - Gomes, Mario N., undated (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Goodwin, Lyndon K., undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Goodman, Nelson G., undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Goodman, Lawrence R., undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Goodman, Sam L., undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Gooch, Alden S., undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Gordon, Henri, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Gordon Jr., Spencer, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Gorfinkel, Joel H., undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Gonzales, Manuel F., undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - German, Barry C., undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Gottlieb, Gregory, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Goyal, Suresh C., undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Grady, Florence E., undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Grand, Bernard, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Grasinger, John E., undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Gray, James J., undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Green, Jeffrey E., undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Department: Child Health
  - Grenbaum, Lennard D., undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Greenberg, Jay B., undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Greenblatt, David, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Greene, Michael D., undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Greenfield, Robert T., undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Greenspan, Robert E., undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Gregory III, George W., undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
    Department:Thoracic and Card. Surg
  - Gresinger, Thomas H., undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Griffin, Calvin L., undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Griffin, Paul, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Grigorian, Haikaz M., undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
    Department: Psych Un-Fl
  - Grim, James F., undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Grollman, Albert H., undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    Department: Med/Asst.Clinical Prof
  - Grosvenor, Mabel H., undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Grondfast, Kenneth, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Guandola, Vincent L., undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Gueriera Charles J., undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Gulati, Amar N., undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Gulbrandsen, Jon A., undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
    Department: Ne Urol.Department: Surg
  - Gulya, Aina J., undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Gutmann, J. Steven, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Hageage, Charles C., undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Hagen, Harold M., undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Haidak, David J., undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Haim, Eduardo, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
    Department: Urolo.
  - Halberstam, Michael J., undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Hall, Debra L., undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Halstead, Clark P., undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Hall Evelyn A., undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
    Department: Child Health and Dev
  - Hardman, George W., undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Harmon, Ronald L., undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Harper, Eugene J., undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Harrison, Thomas A., undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
    Int. Department: Med
  - Hartman, Thomas L., undated (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Hartwell, Patricia, undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Haut, Donald D., undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Haut, Michael J., undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Havell, Thomas C., undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
    Department:Hematolo
  - Hecht, Barry I., undated (Box 22, Folder 56)
    Department:Renal Department: Med
  - Heckman, Bernard, undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Heilen, Robert J., undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
    Department:Ortho sur
  - Helfrich, George B., undated (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Hendren Robert L., undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Herman, John D., undated (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Herskovic, Arnold M., undated (Box 22, Folder 62)
    Department: Rad/Asst. Prof
  - Herzberg, Joseph H., undated (Box 22, Folder 63)
    Department: Psych/Asst. Clinical Prof.
  - Hewitt III, John H., undated (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Hirsch, Florie, undated (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Hirschfeld, Robert M., undated (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Hoffman, Howard A., undated (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Hogg, Judith E., undated (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Holland, Peter M., undated (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Holtz, Albert I., undated (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Homer, Daryl R., undated (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Hookman, Perry, undated (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Hopkins, Ernest, undated (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Horwitz, Stuart L., undated (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Hsiao, Dorothy, undated (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Huberman, Richard, undated (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Huene, Phyllis A., undated (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Huffman, Richard M., undated (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Humphreys, Charles, undated (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Hunter Jr., Allan A., undated (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Hurwitz, Shepard R., undated (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Hurwitz, Gilbert E., undated (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Hurwitz, William E., undated (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Husain, Khalid M., undated (Box 22, Folder 84)
    Department: Surg.
  - Hamner, Lewis, undated (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Hanfling, Carl, undated (Box 22, Folder 86)
    Department: Pediatrics
  - Hannush, Sadder B., undated (Box 22, Folder 87)
    Department:Ophth
  - Hanson, Charles D., undated (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Hanson, Kermit H., undated (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Hardman, George White, undated (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Hutton, John E., undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Indrisano, Jeffrey P., undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Ingham, Donald W., undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Ingram, Virginia G., undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Department: Ped N.B.
  - Isaacson, Benjamin, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Isaacson, Daniel, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Isada, Nelson B., undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Izanec, James J., undated (Box 23, Folder 8)